RG 062:111, Town of Plymouth
Connecticut State Library
Town of Plymouth records
1795-1935
Connecticut State Library
Plymouth (Conn.)
27.5 cubic feet
Tax and school records for the town of Plymouth.
RG062_111
T000279
Historical Note
The town of Plymouth was incorporated in May 1795 and was taken from Watertown.
Scope and Content
Tax and school records for the town of Plymouth.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Plymouth -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Plymouth -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Plymouth -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Plymouth -- Registers; Schools -- Connecticut -- Plymouth -- History -- Sources
Places:
Plymouth (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1795-1935
  - Tax abstract, 1795; 1 volume (photostat)
  - Tax abstract, 1795; copies 2 and 3 (photostat) (Box Box 1)
  - State, Town and Society rate bill, 1798 (Box Box 1)
  - First School District records, 1844-1867 (Box Box 1)
  - Individual tax lists, 1924-1935; 44 volumes
    The individual tax lists are not boxed.
    - A-I, 1924; 1 volume
    - S-Z, 1924; 1 volume
    - A-J, 1925; 1 volume
    - P-Z, 1925; 1 volume
    - A-J, 1926; 1 volume
    - Q-Z, 1926; 1 volume
    - A-H, 1927; 1 volume
    - I-R, 1927; 1 volume
    - A-H, 1928; 1 volume
    - I-R, 1928; 1 volume
    - S-Z, 1928; 1 volume
    - A-D, 1929; 1 volume
    - E-M, 1929; 1 volume
    - Mc-Z, 1929; 1 volume
    - Non Resident, 1929; 1 volume
    - A-C, 1930; 1 volume
    - D-J, 1930; 1 volume
    - K-M, 1930; 1 volume
    - Mc-S, 1930; 1 volume
    - T-Z and non-resident, 1930; 1 volume
    - A-C, 1931; 1 volume
    - D-J, 1931; 1 volume
    - K-M, 1931; 1 volume
    - N-S, 1931; 1 volume
    - T-Z and non-resident, 1931; 1 volume
    - A-C, 1932; 1 volume
    - D-J, 1932; 1 volume
    - K-MC, 1932; 1 volume
    - N-S, 1932; 1 volume
    - T-Z and non-resident, 1932; 1 volume
    - A-F, 1933; 1 volume
    - G-L, 1933; 1 volume
    - M-S, 1933; 1 volume
    - T-Z And non-resident, 1933; 1 volume
    - A-C, 1934; 1 volume
    - D-J, 1934; 1 volume
    - K-M, 1934; 1 volume
    - N-S, 1934; 1 volume
    - T-Z and non-resident, 1934; 1 volume
    - A-C, 1935; 1 volume
    - D-J, 1935; 1 volume
    - K-O, 1935; 1 volume
    - P-U, 1935; 1 volume
    - V-Z and non-resident, 1935; 1 volume